# Josh Engert

IT All-Rounder

I am aiming gain an entry level role that will challenge me and allow me to use my education, skills and past experiences in a way that is mutually beneficial to both myself and my employer and allow for future growth and advancement.

**\** 0274202042

# jdev.co.nz

joshengert@hotmail.com

Kingsland, Auckland

#### **SKILLS**

**Customer Service Expertise** 

Team Leader/Problem Solver

**Inventory Management** 

Windows/Linux/OS X

Automation and Scripting

Continuous Improvement

Hardware Set-up/Deployment

#### **HOBBIES**

**DJing** 

Kickboxing

**Card Collecting** 

**Rock Climbing** 

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

## **CCNA (Currently Studying)**

Cisco Systems

Embedded Systems Essentials with Arm Professional Certificate

edX

# First Aid Level 1

St. Johns

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## BurgerFuel, Mount Eden

Day Shift Manager

(December 2015 - Present)

In charge of maintaining inventory levels, contacting suppliers, and ensuring a high level of customer satisfaction while setting up the following night shift to run as smoothly as possible. Often called upon to solve IT problems by other members of staff and the franchisee

#### EB Games, Newmarket

Senior Sales Associate

(October 2021 - Present)

Senior member of staff in one of the busiest stores in the country. Consistently met standards for KPIs and provided a high level of customer service. Relied upon as a keyholder to open and close the store.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Media Design School, Auckland

Bachelor of Software Engineering

Currently deferred, final year to complete

### Rotorua Boys' High School

NCEA Level 3 (Merit Endorsed)

(January 2010 - November 2014)

(February 2018 - June 2022)

# **NOTABLE PROJECTS**

## TinyDJ

A credit card sized DJ controller created using the ATMega32u4 microcontroller, that outputs midi signals to work with most major DJ software. Required understanding of basic electrical engineering concepts and an understanding of microcontrollers and analogue/digital input.

#### Van-Go

A first person puzzle platformer developed in Unity using C#, based on the art style of Vincent van Gogh. In charge of the players movement mechanics and level design. Required a good understanding of geometry and physics.

## **3D Cloth Simulator**

Used my knowledge of physics and geometry to create a cloth simulator with wind simulation in C++ with OpenGL.

#### **REFERENCES**

Matt Cornes Franchisee, BurgerFuel 021 300 124 **Guy Stitchbury** Store Manager, EB Games 027 603 6677